prizelive.com 2016-01-19

# Privacy Policy | instaGC

Day Online Solutions, LLC (the "Company") owns and operates instaGC.com. The Company is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is to detail the information the Company might gather about individuals who visit instaGC.com, how that information is used, and our disclosure practices. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to websites owned and operated by the Company, and not to the sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links. By using instaGC.com, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service, which are incorporated by reference herein to this Privacy Policy.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily provide to us. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. send you a reward). Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may withdraw consent at any time.

## What Personal Information We Collect

When you sign up for the instaGC site, you will be required to share information that identifies you personally. "Personal Information" refers to any information that lets us know the specifics of who you are and which can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Examples of Personal Information include, without limitation, your first name together with your last name, your mailing address, your email address, your birthdate, your gender, your phone number, your SSN (only used if you are from USA and have earned over $600+ in rewards in a given year - for tax purposes), and your bank account information (only obtained if you choose to receive a direct deposit reward).

## What Personal Information We Will Never Collect

The Company will never ask for any of the following pieces of information, during registration or participation: DLN (drivers license number), SSN (social security number) - except for tax purposes, credit card information, passport number, or photo. However - at times you may be asked to submit ID verification that may include items stated above - so feel free to blur/hide the information as desired.

## When We Collect Personal Information

In order to use instaGC.com, you must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Additional information will also be asked in order to use our services. If you don't provide some of the Personal Information the Company asks for (e.g. your name, your mailing address, your email address, your birthdate), it may be unable to provide you with the Company's goods or services.

## Correspondence

If you contact the Company, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address for archival purposes but will not use, transfer or sell your email address except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Third Party Sites

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. You may visit the following sites [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) and/or [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to opt-out of cookies.

## Sharing

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Mergers; Business Transitions

In the event the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' Personal Information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred, unless such a transfer will violate any applicable law.

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (users under the age of 13)**

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with the Company policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT: 

\- Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or   
\- Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties; 

We request that children under the age of 13 not submit any Personal Information to us. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers. 

## Opt Out

You can review, correct, change or remove any personal registration information you provide to the Company. In order to "opt-out" and elect not to receive future communications from us, please email us at contact@instagc.com. You can request access to, and correction of, your personal information by contacting the Company as follows: 

instaGC.com  
PO Box 48  
Sellersburg, Indiana 47172-0048  
contact@instagc.com 

Please note that as long as you remain an instaGC.com user, opting not to receive email does not exempt you from receiving administrative emails, which include, but are not limited to, notices about vital service and status changes or alterations to the Company's Terms. 

## Notification of Changes

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. 

Last Updated: 10/28/2015
